http://www.edwardjones.com/privacy/index.html

Continuing to serve you in a thoughtful way.
Throughout the challenges of recent months, we’ve continued to safely serve investors’ needs. We are thoughtfully evaluating our office openings and in-person appointments. Learn More
Close Message
Edward JonesHide Menu
Secure Login
Find an Advisor
Value of a Financial Advisor
Investments & Services
Preparing for Your Future
Market News & Guidance
Privacy
At Edward Jones, we understand that confidentiality is key in any financial relationship. We recognize that your personal and financial data is your private information, and we are committed to keeping it secure and confidential.
Please take a moment to review our privacy practices. If you have any questions, contact your local Edward Jones financial advisor or call 1-855-898-6102.
Edward Jones & Edward Jones Trust Company Privacy Notice
Learn about how we collect, share and protect your personal information.
Privacy Policy
Learn about our privacy practices that apply to website visitors.
Consumer Data Rights Request
This portal, powered by OneTrust, complies with the requirements of the California Consumer Privacy Act and allows you to submit your consumer data rights request to the Edward Jones Privacy team
Protecting Clients' Personal Information
Learn what Edward Jones does to protect our clients' personal information, as well as steps investors should take.
Fraud Awareness and Prevention
Education is your best protection against consumer fraud. Learn more about scams and how to protect yourself.
Your Financial Advisor
,
